<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>malay dhamelia</title>
    <link>http://www.malaydhamelia.in/</link>
    <description>Recent content on malay dhamelia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 12:13:30 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.malaydhamelia.in/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Covid information data visualisations are amusements</title>
      <link>http://www.malaydhamelia.in/blog/post-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 12:13:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.malaydhamelia.in/blog/post-1/</guid>
      <description>Historically, humans have endured several epidemics and pandemics. What makes the CoVID 19 epidemic different is, it&amp;rsquo;s co-existence with the information age. The age where we live between the concepts of technocracy and technopoly as explained by Neil Postman in his book Technopoly: The Surrender of Culture to Technology. I bring this here as this idea sparked from the conversations one catches daily, and the observed unusuality of it in recent times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interventions for awareness of noise pollution</title>
      <link>http://www.malaydhamelia.in/work/post-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 12:13:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.malaydhamelia.in/work/post-6/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Sonic environment consisting of various sounds ranging from music and natural sounds to artificial sounds is an integral part of any geography. It is a reflection of people living in the location as well as an influencer of culture in that location. To assess the perception of a person or people of context offered by that location, a soundscape assessment is performed that majorly involve likert based questions for pleasantness, annoyance, appropriateness and so forth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cultural Domain Analysis for Soundscape Assessment</title>
      <link>http://www.malaydhamelia.in/work/post-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 12:13:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.malaydhamelia.in/work/post-4/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Sonic environment consisting of various sounds ranging from music and natural sounds to artificial sounds is an integral part of any geography. It is a reflection of people living in the location as well as an influencer of culture in that location. To assess the perception of a person or people of context offered by that location, a soundscape assessment is performed that majorly involve likert based questions for pleasantness, annoyance, appropriateness and so forth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interventions to change handwashing behaviour</title>
      <link>http://www.malaydhamelia.in/work/post-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2017 12:13:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.malaydhamelia.in/work/post-5/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Hands come in contact with a variety of surfaces and fluids. This makes hands, a primary vector of many communicable diseases. Acute diarrhoeal diseases, acute respiratory diseases can be prevented by a simple habit of washing hands at appropriate times. This habit is very essential for households of urban slums and rural areas since the surrounding is an ideal hotbed for pathogens. The effect of hand washing is acknowledged by medical experts and the world health organisation (WHO).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Epidemic Informatics: Real time visualisation of epidemics</title>
      <link>http://www.malaydhamelia.in/work/post-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2017 12:13:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.malaydhamelia.in/work/post-2/</guid>
      <description>Overview Preventing epidemic from occurring and spreading is the one of the major motives of any government health ward. Collecting information about the epidemics is done via manual reporting in the current state. Information about epidemics require faster ways of reporting to take actions and prevent it from spreading. We leveraged the increased usage of smartphone to increase a faster reporting of epidemics in a city.
We conducted user studies to understand the existing flow of information between entities ranging from the epidemic cell to local foot soldiers over a period of two weeks to design and develop an application that will allow faster reporting with very less cognitive load on the foot soldiers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pulse: Crowd sensing for smarter cities</title>
      <link>http://www.malaydhamelia.in/work/post-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2017 12:13:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.malaydhamelia.in/work/post-3/</guid>
      <description>Overview The advent of smart cities has increased the demand for agile and effective governance. This paper presents a prototype at the proof of concept stage, called “Pulse”. The system comprises of – a mobile app for citizens to submit feedback, a web dashboard for district administrators and government bodies to push close-ended questions based on locality, gender, age group and time, and a network of eddystone beacons that pushes close-ended questions about urban spaces, creating a hyperlocal crowdsensing framework in the Indian context.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>User study: Technological opportunities to support kirana stores</title>
      <link>http://www.malaydhamelia.in/work/post-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2016 12:13:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.malaydhamelia.in/work/post-1/</guid>
      <description>Overview While modern trade has been growing in India over the last 25 years, small grocery stores (also known as kirana shops) continue to have over 90% of the market share. An interesting practice in these stores is that they provide credit to their customers, which is a major draw for some of their loyal customers. However, this practice often leads to a crunch of working capital for the shopkeeper. Could these traditional credit practices be better supported with use of technology?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>