<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>User Study on malay dhamelia</title>
    <link>http://www.malaydhamelia.in/tags/user-study/</link>
    <description>Recent content in User Study on malay dhamelia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 12:13:36 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.malaydhamelia.in/tags/user-study/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Interventions for awareness of noise pollution</title>
      <link>http://www.malaydhamelia.in/work/post-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 12:13:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.malaydhamelia.in/work/post-6/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Sonic environment consisting of various sounds ranging from music and natural sounds to artificial sounds is an integral part of any geography. It is a reflection of people living in the location as well as an influencer of culture in that location. To assess the perception of a person or people of context offered by that location, a soundscape assessment is performed that majorly involve likert based questions for pleasantness, annoyance, appropriateness and so forth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interventions to change handwashing behaviour</title>
      <link>http://www.malaydhamelia.in/work/post-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2017 12:13:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.malaydhamelia.in/work/post-5/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Hands come in contact with a variety of surfaces and fluids. This makes hands, a primary vector of many communicable diseases. Acute diarrhoeal diseases, acute respiratory diseases can be prevented by a simple habit of washing hands at appropriate times. This habit is very essential for households of urban slums and rural areas since the surrounding is an ideal hotbed for pathogens. The effect of hand washing is acknowledged by medical experts and the world health organisation (WHO).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>User study: Technological opportunities to support kirana stores</title>
      <link>http://www.malaydhamelia.in/work/post-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2016 12:13:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.malaydhamelia.in/work/post-1/</guid>
      <description>Overview While modern trade has been growing in India over the last 25 years, small grocery stores (also known as kirana shops) continue to have over 90% of the market share. An interesting practice in these stores is that they provide credit to their customers, which is a major draw for some of their loyal customers. However, this practice often leads to a crunch of working capital for the shopkeeper. Could these traditional credit practices be better supported with use of technology?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>