<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Play on Malay Dhamelia</title>
    <link>/play/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Play on Malay Dhamelia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/play/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ad-ventura</title>
      <link>/play/ad-ventura/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/play/ad-ventura/</guid>
      <description>Whatever is limited can be traded 1/ &amp;#8853; 1/ Scarcity being the extereme case of limited-ness .
This human trait of finding value in what is limited has primal roots. Ancient trade began when people saw value in shells, cowrie money. ⊕  Cowrie trading in old Kolkata (কলকাতা)    People collected those shells from wherever they can and stored it for future trades. They were passed as heirlooms initially to store the rarity and once it was accepted as a medium of exchange, they were traded for good and collected as a store of value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amabie</title>
      <link>/play/amabie/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 13:09:13 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/play/amabie/</guid>
      <description>Hope is lost. People are scared of the unknown virus, uncertain about what is to come, and are scared of deaths. People lost faith in the government /1 &amp;#8853; 1/ From managing health infrastructure to managing migrant workers  . State governments, although are pulling all-nighters and trying their best, are failing in the face of calamity. ⊕  Amabie  Amabie is a yokai with three legs, a body with scales and a beaked face.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research from IDC</title>
      <link>/play/idc_gj/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/play/idc_gj/</guid>
      <description>IDC completed 50 years in 2019. The celebration was ceremonious. Incidentally, I re-joined IDC as a PhD student with Prof Girish. I thought of contributing to the celebration by analysing research contributed by IDC to different domains. It started out as an idea during one of my conversations with Prof Anirudha.
The post is structured as follows:
 Why to look at the history of research? Ways to look at the research of an organisation?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vyartha</title>
      <link>/play/vyartha/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2014 13:09:13 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/play/vyartha/</guid>
      <description>व्यर्थ // વ્યર્થ // vyarth (in vain) We called it Vyartha because this is the feeling that made us compose the book. It is an existential story of one Utc Singhal who did not fear the emotions and looked through the reality to find deeper meanings. He is a man of questions, and a courage to find answers. He does not shy away from the medium or the message. This is a story of Malay who was always curious about what goes in the mind of Utc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>